Guide to the Picture File, 1700s-1980s and undated RL.01025
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- People Series, 1700s-1970s; 1
  - Tracy, Edward Dott, 1800s, card photograph (Box 34, Folder M1671)
  - Trimble, Isaac Ridgeway, 1800s, card photograph (Box 34, Folder M1672)
  - Trimble, Robert, 1889, engraving (Box 34, Folder M1673)
  - Troup, George Michael, 1800s, engraving (Box 34, Folder M1674)
  - True, Herbert H., 1800s, card photograph (Box 34, Folder M1675)
  - Tucker, Jane Skelton (Ellis) and Tucker, (Nathaniel) Beverly, 1901 Oct. 15 and undated, 2 card photographs (Box 34, Folder M1676)
    The smaller photograph is from the C. C. Clay Papers; the larger from the Munford-Ellis Papers.
  - Turner, Jesse, Sr., 1800s, 1 black-and-white photograph (Box 34, Folder M1677)
  - Turner, Jesse, Sr., 1800s, card photograph (Box 46)
  - Turner, Rebecca J. (Allen), 1855 and undated, 1 black-and-white photograph and 1 card photograph (Box 34, Folder M1678)
    The black-and-white photograph was copied from a daguerrotype.
  - Twain, Mark and His Boyhood Home, 1902 (Box 19, Folder M717)
  - Twain, Mark: Cave (Box 19, Folder M717)
  - Twiggs, David E., 1800s, 1 black-and-white illustration and 1 engraving (Box 34, Folder M1679)
  - Two photographic portraits, unidentified, undated, black-and-white photograph (Oversize-folder 45)
  - Tyler, John, 1863 and 1800s, 2 engravings (Box 34, Folder M1680)
  - U.S. House of Representatives, 1860, black-and-white photo (Oversize-folder 56)
  - U.S. Senate Chamber, undated, black-and-white photo (Oversize-folder 18)
    Includes key for identifying senators in the photo.
  - Umberto I, King of Italy, undated, card photograph (Box 34, Folder M1681)
  - Underwood, Washington Quincy, undated, card photograph (Box 46)
  - Unidentified group photograph, 1890s-1900s, black-and-white photograph (Box 55)
    Taken outdoors.
  - Unidentified large group of well-dressed men outdoors, probably Philadelphia, with dog, circa 1910, black-and-white photograph (Box 58, Folder M1824)
    Photographer H.[enry?] Troth, Philadelphia. Possibly a platinum print. Unknown collection provenance.
  - Unidentified man, 3/4 profile portrait, 1923?, black-and-white photograph (Box 58, Folder M1805)
    Portrait is enclosed in cardstock portfolio inscribed with studio name, Dworshak, Duluth. Louis F. Dworshak was a portrait photographer in Duluth, Minnesota, from 1893 into the 1950s.
  - Unidentified young woman riding sidesaddle on horse, circa 1910 (Box 58, Folder M1822)
  - Unidentified woman in military uniform, undated, black-and-white photo (Box 56)
  - Union Commanders: Farragut, Meade..., 1884, black-and-white photographic illustration (Box 46)
  - Union Naval Commanders, 1800s, engraving (Box 34, Folder M1682)
  - Untermeyer, Samuel, 1900s, black-and-white photographic illustration (Box 34, Folder M1683)
  - Updike, John Hoyer, 1900s, black-and-white photograph (Box 34, Folder M1684)
    Gift of Professor Clarence Gohdes.
  - Valentine, Edward V., 1900s, card photograph (Box 34, Folder M1685)
    Transferred from the Albert Aylor Papers.
  - Van Buren, Martin, 1800s, engraving (Box 34, Folder M1686)
  - Van Dorn, Earl, 1800s, card photograph (Box 34, Folder M1687)
  - Van Etten, Solomon, 1864 Apr. 12, card photograph (Box 34, Folder M1688)
    Solomon Van Etten, 56th N.Y. Inf. (Tenth Legion).
  - Van Noppen, Charles Leonard, undated, engraving (Box 46)
    From the Charles L. Van Noppen Mss. Includes signature of Charles Van Noppen.
  - Van Noppen, Leonard Charles, undated, 1 engraving, 1 black-and-white photographic illustration and 1 card photograph (Box 34, Folder M1689)
    The engraving and illustration are both from the Charles L. Van Noppen Mss.
  - Vance, Zebulon Baird and Vance, Harriet N. (Espy), 1800s, 2 card photographs (Box 34, Folder M1692)
  - Vance, Zebulon Baird, 1876, card photograph (Box 34, Folder M1690)
  - Vance, Zebulon Baird, et al., 1897 Oct. 20, card photograph (Box 34, Folder M1691)
  - Vanderbilt University -- Medical Students, 1885-1886, card photograph (Box 34, Folder M1693)
  - Vanderbilt, William Henry, 1800s, engraving (Box 34, Folder M1694)
    Transferred from the C. C. Jones, Jr. Scrapbook.
  - Vansittart, Nicholas, First Baron Bexley, 1831, engraving (Box 34, Folder M1695)
  - Vassali, Count, 1820 Nov. 10, engraving (Box 34, Folder M1696)
  - Vauban, Sebastian le Prestre, Marquis de, 1800s, 2 engravings (Box 34, Folder M1697)
  - Vickers, Genora Ann (Wood), undated, black-and-white illustration (Oversize-folder 20)
  - Vickers, William Gaston, undated, black-and-white illustration (Oversize-folder 20)
  - Victoria, Queen of Great Britain, undated, color illustration (Box 34, Folder M1698)
  - Villiers, George, First Duke of Buckingham (1592-1628), 1825 Sept. 1, engraving (Box 46)
  - Volunteers of "Lazarus Institute"..., 1900s, card photograph (Box 42)
  - Von Schwartze, Charles H., undated, black-and-white photograph (Box 34, Folder M1701)
  - Voorhees, Daniel Wolsey, undated, card photograph (Box 34, Folder M1702)
  - Wagoner, Charles Boyd, 1913 Sept., 1922, 1800s and undated, 5 card photographs (Box 34, Folder M1703)
  - Waite, Morrison Remick, 1800s, engraving (Box 35, Folder M1704)
  - Walker, Gilbert Carlton, 1871 June 3, card photograph (Box 35, Folder M1705)
  - Walker, H. T., circa 1860s, card photograph (Box 35, Folder M1706)
  - Walker, Norman, 1800s, card photograph (Box 35, Folder M1707)
  - Walker, Ralph, 1803 Dec. 1, engraving (Box 35, Folder M1708)
  - Wallace, Henry Agard, 1900s, clipping (Box 35, Folder M1709)
  - Wallace, W. H., 1876 Nov. 28, card photograph (Box 46)
    Photograph depicts Wallace and other members of the S.C. legislature of 1876.
  - Wallace, W. H., undated, black-and-white photograph (Box 35, Folder M1710)
    Includes W. H. Wallace's signature.
  - Walpole, Robert, Earl of Oxford, 1836 Dec. 1 and 1800s, engraving (Box 35, Folder M1711)
  - Walpole, Robert, Earl of Oxford, undated, engraving (Box 46)
  - Walsingham, Sir Francis (circa 1530-1590), 1824 Apr. 1, engraving (Box 46)
    Removed from M1712.
  - Walton, George, undated, 4 engravings and 1 black-and-white photograph (Box 35, Folder M1713)
    One of these engravings is from the Georgia Historical Society, and another engraving is from Jones: Biographical Sketches of the Delegates from Georgia to the Continental Congress.
  - Warburton, Amber Arthur, 1898-1976, 1900s, 5 black-and-white photographs (Box 35, Folder M1714)
  - Warburton, Amber Arthur, 1898-1976, 1900s, 2 black-and-white photographs and 1 broadside (Box 46)
  - Warburton, Amber Arthur, 1898-1976, 1920 June 21-1922 Sept. 1, 3 diplomas (Box 35, Folder M1714)
  - Warburton, Amber Arthur, 1898-1976, 1928 and 1900s, 9 black-and-white photographs and 4 postcards (Box 35, Folder M1714)
  - Warburton, Amber Arthur, 1898-1976, 1935 July and 1900s, 5 black-and-white photographs (Box 35, Folder M1714)
  - Warner, Hiram, 1800s, engraving (Box 35, Folder M1715)
  - Warren, Joseph, 1835, engraving (Box 35, Folder M1716)
  - Warrington, Lewis, 1815 Oct. 2, engraving (Box 35, Folder M1717)
    See picture of the 'Peacock,' whick Lewis Warrington commanded during the War of 1812.
  - Washington, Andrew Coyle, 1800s, card photograph (Box 35, Folder M1718)
  - Washington, Bushrod, 1891, engraving (Box 35, Folder M1719)
  - Washington, George, 1800s and 1836, 5 engravings and 1 color illustration (Box 35, Folder M1720.1)
    One engraving is from John Marshall's "The Life of George Washington...," Vol. 1, 2nd ed., Philadelphia, James Crissy, 1836. One engraving is from Jones: Biographical Sketches of the Delegates from Georgia to the Continental Congress. See also M1794 for an additional engraving and ALN.
  - Washington, George, 1800s, 1796-1893, 4 engravings and 1 color illustration (Box 35, Folder M1720.3)
    Two engravings are from Jared Spark's "The Writings of George Washington...," Vol. 2, 1834. One engraving is from "Sons of the American Revolution," New York, Year Book, 1893.
  - Washington, George, 1800s, 1833-1834 and 1900s, 5 engravings and 1 black-and-white photograph (Box 35, Folder M1720.2)
    Two engravings are from Jared Spark's "The Writings of George Washington...," Vol. 3, 1834 and 1847. One engraving is from Jones: Biographical Sketches of the Delegates from Georgia to the Continental Congress. The photograph is from the Socialist Party Records.
  - Washington, George, and Abraham Lincoln, "Columbia's noblest sons," 1865, black-and-white lithograph (Box 61)
  - Washington, Mabel, 1890, card photograph (Box 29, Folder M1374)
    Portrait of African American woman
  - Washington, William, 1800s, engraving (Box 35, Folder M1721)
  - Watson, R., undated, engraving (Box 35, Folder M1722)
    Transferred from the Eugene Marshall Hendrix Mss.
  - Watson, Sereno, undated, 2 card photographs (Box 35, Folder M1723)
  - Watts-Dunton, Walter Theodore, undated, black-and-white photographic illustration (Box 35, Folder M1726)
  - Watts, George Washington, 1900s, 1clippingand 1 black-and-white photograph (Box 35, Folder M1724)
    The photograph has a negative available.
  - Watts, Richard Cannon, undated, card photograph (Box 35, Folder M1725)
    Transferred from the William Watts Ball Papers.
  - Wayne, Anthony, 1858, 1863, 1796 and 1800s, 6 engravings (Box 35, Folder M1727)
    One engraving is from Vol. 2 of "History of the United States of America" by Henry William Elion, published in N.Y. in 1905. Two engravings are from Jones: Biographical Sketches of the Delegates from Georgia to the Continental Congress.
  - Wayne, James M., 1890, 2 engravings (Box 35, Folder M1728)
  - Webster, Daniel, 1800s and circa 1868, 5 engravings (Box 35, Folder M1729)
    One engraving is from Alexander H. Stephens' "A Constitutional View of the War Between the States...," Vol. 1.
  - Wedderburn, Alexander, First Earl of Rosslyn, 1796 July 1, engraving (Box 35, Folder M1730)
  - Weedon, Miss Howard, 1800s, card photograph (Box 35, Folder M1731)
  - Weeks, Stephen Beauregard, 1900s, 2 card photographs (Box 35, Folder M1732)
  - Welch, William Henry, undated, black-and-white photograph (Box 35, Folder M1733)
  - Welles, Gideon, 1865, engraving (Box 35, Folder M1734)
  - Wellesley, Arthur [Duke of Wellington], 1836, engraving (Box 42)
  - Wesley, Charles (1707-1788), 1800s, engraving (Box 35, Folder M1735)
  - Wesley, John -- Rev., 1800s, color lithograph (Box 42)
  - Wesley, John, 1790, 1775 Jan. 20 and 1800s, 4 engravings and 1 black-and-white photograph (Box 35, Folder M1736)
    All of these items have negatives available. The first two engravings were loaned by Mrs. Marmaduke Floyd. The original folder included several pages of biographical information on John Wesley; these were replaced by photocopies.
  - Wesley, Samuel, 1836, 1800s and undated, 3 engravings (Box 35, Folder M1737)
    The last engraving is a gift from Frank C. Brown.
  - West, Benjamin, 1820-1823 Jan. 1 and 1800s, 5 engravings (Box 35, Folder M1738)
  - Wheat, Leo, 1800s, card photograph (Box 35, Folder M1739)
  - Wheeler, Joseph, 1800s, 2 engravings, 1 black-and-white photographic illustration and 1 black-and-white photograph (Box 36, Folder M1740)
  - White, Hugh Lawson, 1800s, engraving (Box 36, Folder M1741)
  - Whitefield, George, 1834 and undated, 4 lithographs (Box 36, Folder M1742.2)
    Three of these lithographs have negatives available. One lithograph was taken from "Memories of Rev. George Whitefield" by John Gillies. New Haven. Whitemore, Buckingham and H. Mansfield, 1834. Two lithographs were taken from Jones: Biographical Sketches of the Delegates from Georgia to the Continental Congress.
  - Whitefield, George, 1834, 1749 and undated, 5 lithographs and 1 black-and-white photograph (Box 36, Folder M1742.1)
    Four of these lithographs have negatives available. Three lithographs were taken from "Memories of Rev. George Whitefield" by John Gillies, New Haven, Whitemore, Buckingham and H. Mansfield, 1834.
  - Whitehead, George, undated, black-and-white illustration (Box 46)
  - Whitehouse, Albert, undated, card photograph (Box 36, Folder M1743)
  - Whittemore, B. F., 1800s, engraving (Box 36, Folder M1744)
  - Whittier, John Greenleaf, undated, 1handbill and 1 black-and-white illustration (Box 36, Folder M1745)
  - Wilberforce, William, 1814 Nov. 1, 1798 Apr. 28 and 1800s, 5 engravings (Box 36, Folder M1746)
  - Wilde, Oscar Fingal O'Flahertie Wills, 1800s, card photograph (Box 36, Folder M1747)
  - Wilde, Richard Henry, 1800s, engraving (Box 36, Folder M1748)
  - Wiley, Isaac William, 1800s, engraving (Box 36, Folder M1749)
  - Wiley, Louis, 1913 Feb. 7, card photograph (Box 46)
  - Wilhelm I (Friedrich), King of Prussia (1688-1740), 1877, card photograph (Box 36, Folder M1750)
  - Wilkes, Charles, 1864, engraving (Box 36, Folder M1751)
  - Wilkie, Wendell Lewis, 1900s, clipping (Box 36, Folder M1757)
  - Wilkie, Wendell, undated, color illustration (Box 46)
    Taken from Fortune magazine.
  - Wilks, Robert, 1800s, 2 engravings (Box 36, Folder M1752)
  - Willard, A. J., 1800s, engraving (Box 36, Folder M1753)
    Contains possibly authentic signature of A. J. Willard.
  - Willard, W. H., 1900s, card photograph (Box 46)
  - William III, King of Great Britain, undated, 2 engravings (Box 36, Folder M1754)
  - William III, King of Great Britain, undated, engraving (Box 46)
  - Williams, Thomas, undated, card photograph (Box 36, Folder M1755)
    Transferred from the George Smith Houston Papers.
  - Willis, Robert H., undated, card photograph (Box 36, Folder M1756)
    Transferred from the 9019 Papers.
  - Wilson, Daniel (1778-1858), 1833, engraving (Box 36, Folder M1758)
  - Wilson, Henry, 1800s, engraving (Box 36, Folder M1759)
    Includes possibly authentic signature of Henry Wilson.
  - Wilson, Woodrow, 1913, May 1914 and 1900s, 2 black-and-white illustrations and 1 black-and-white photograph (Box 36, Folder M1760)
    Transferred from the Marmaduke Floyd Collection. The first illustration is from "The Journal of the American Historical Society," Vol. XII. New York, 1913.
  - Winter, Cornelius, undated, engraving (Box 36, Folder M1761)
  - Winterhalter, A. G., Admiral, U. S. N., 1916 Jan. 10, black-and-white photograph (Box 36, Folder M1762)
  - Wirt, William, 1863 and 1800s, 3 engravings (Box 36, Folder M1763)
  - Wise, Henry Alexander, 1800s, 2 engravings (Box 36, Folder M1764)
  - Witherspoon, John, undated, engraving (Box 36, Folder M1765)
  - Wolf, Frederick Adolphus, circa 1938, black-and-white photograph (Box 36, Folder M1766)
  - Wolfe, Thomas Clayton, 1937, black-and-white photograph (Box 36, Folder M1768)
    From the Hubert H. Hayes Papers. Signed by Mabel (Wolfe) Wheaton.
  - Wolfe, Thomas Clayton, and Julia Elizabeth (Westall) Wolfe, 1937, black-and-white photograph (Box 36, Folder M1769)
  - Wolfe, Thomas Clayton, undated, handbill (Box 36, Folder M1767)
  - Wolsey, Thomas, et al., undated, engraving (Box 36, Folder M1770)
  - Woods, W. B., 1890, engraving (Box 36, Folder M1771)
  - Wool, John Ellis, 1859, engraving (Box 36, Folder M1772)
    Contains possibly authentic signature of John Ellis Wool.
  - Woolner, Thomas, 1861 and 1800s, 2 black-and-white illustrations (Box 36, Folder M1773)
  - Woolsey, Theodore D., 1800s, engraving (Box 36, Folder M1774)
  - Worth, Jonathan, 1800s, engraving (Box 36, Folder M1775)
  - Worth, William Jenkins, 1848, engraving (Box 36, Folder M1776)
  - Wrangham, Francis (1769-1842), 1838, engraving (Box 36, Folder M1777)
  - Wright, G. W., 1800s, engraving (Box 36, Folder M1778)
  - Wright, Marcus J., 1800s, engraving (Box 36, Folder M1779)
  - Wright, Richard Harvey, 1800s, 2 black-and-white photographs (Box 36, Folder M1780)
  - Wright, Richard Harvey, undated, black-and-white photographic illustration (Box 36, Folder M1781)
    Copy of a photograph from the American Historical Society. Includes possibly authentic signature of Richard Harvey Wright.
  - Wriothesley, Henry, Third Earl of Southhampton (1563-1624), 1800s, engraving (Box 36, Folder M1782)
    One of William Shakespeare's patrons.
  - Wylie, Walker Gill, circa 1884, card photograph (Box 36, Folder M1783)
  - Wythe, George, 1800s, engraving (Box 36, Folder M1784)
  - Yancey, William Lowndes, 1800s, lithograph (Box 36, Folder M1785)
  - Yarbrough, Richard and Tabitha (Johns), 1800s, 2 card photographs and 2 black-and-white photographs (Box 36, Folder M1786)
  - Yohannan, Mar., Bishop of Ooroomiah, 1842, lithograph (Box 42)
  - Young, Pierce Manning Butler, 1800s, 1 black-and-white photographic illustration and 1 engraving (Box 36, Folder M1787)
    The illustration is from Charles E. Jones' Scrapbook.
  - Zacharias, Peter, 1800s, card photograph (Box 36, Folder M1788)
  - Zollicoffer, Felix Kirk, 1800s, card photograph (Box 36, Folder M1789)
- Socialist Party Records, 1800s-1980s; 1
  Originally part of the Socialist Party Records, this series was added to the Picture File in the 1980s and remains intellectually distinct from the other series in the collection. It has two subseries: General and People. The General Subseries consists of images depicting a variety of subjects, ranging from Civil Rights protests in the U.S. to news photographs of the Nazi military buildup in the early 1930s. This subseries also contains images of Socialist Party headquarters, parades, and strikes. The People Subseries contains portraits of various socialist leaders throughout the party's history (both national and regional), with a large amount of material focusing on the life of five-time U.S. presidential candidate Eugene V. Debs. Also included in this subseries are groups of socialist legislators as well as assembled socialist conventions and delegations. The vast majority of the images in this series portray various events and individuals in Socialist Party history; however, there are also a few items which depict places of socialist interest, such as the city of Vienna or the party headquarters in Chicago. Images in this series are chiefly photographic; other formats include handbills, clippings, sketches, black-and-white illustrations, a viewbook, and postcards.
  - General, 1
    - British Labor Party, 1936, 1949 and undated, 6 black-and-white photographs (Box 11, Folder M337)
    - Civil Rights pictures, 1960 Feb. 27-Mar. 31, 4 black-and-white photographs (Box 11, Folder M338.1)
    - Civil Rights pictures, 1960 May 12 and undated, 4 black-and-white photographs (Box 11, Folder M338.2)
    - Civil Rights pictures, 1965, Berkeley, Cal., undated, 3 black-and-white photographs (Box 11, Folder M339)
    - European Socialism - Czechoslovakia, 1900s, 3 black-and-white photographs (Box 11, Folder M340)
    - German Army and Navy - 1930s, 1933 Feb. 9-1934 Aug. 6 and undated, 6 black-and-white photographs (Box 11, Folder M341)
    - Havana, Cuba, 1960 Sept. 2, black-and-white photograph (Box 11, Folder M342)
    - International Socialist Convention at Vienna, 1957 July, 2 black-and-white photographs (Box 11, Folder M343)
    - Lafayette's Tomb, Paris, 1925 May 31, black-and-white photograph (Box 11, Folder M344)
    - May Day rallies, 1936, 1947 and 1900s, 2 black-and-white photographs and 2 sketches (Box 11, Folder M345.1)
    - May Day rallies, 1936 and 1948, 4 black-and-white photographs (Box 11, Folder M345.2)
    - Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1949 Mar. 15 and 1900s, 3 black-and-white photographs (Box 11, Folder M346)
    - Socialist presidential campaigns, undated, black-and-white photograph (Box 11, Folder M347)
      Photograph depicts campaign buttons for Socialist presidential candidates from 1900 to 1956.
    - Spanish Civil War, circa 1930s and 1955, 4 black-and-white photographs (Box 11, Folder M348.1)
    - Spanish Civil War, circa 1930s, 5 black-and-white photographs (Box 11, Folder M348.2)
    - Spanish protest for confederated Spanish societies, 1960, 2 black-and-white photographs (Box 11, Folder M349)
    - Unidentified individuals, 1957 Nov. and undated, 12 black-and-white photographs (Box 11, Folder M350.1)
    - Unidentified individuals, 1945 Oct. 3 and undated, 7 black-and-white photographs (Box 11, Folder M350.2)
    - Unidentified individuals, 1939 June 27, 1947 Feb. 7, and undated, 6 black-and-white photographs (Box 11, Folder M350.3)
    - Unity Convention, 1956 June 8-10 and 1957, 9 black-and-white photographs (Box 11, Folder M351.1)
    - Unity Convention, 1957, 6 black-and-white photographs (Box 11, Folder M351.2)
    - Unity Convention, 1957, 8 black-and-white photographs (Box 11, Folder M351.3)
    - Unity Convention, 1957, 1957, 12 black-and-white photographs (Box 12, Folder M351.4)
    - Unity Convention, 1957, 12 black-and-white photographs (Box 12, Folder M351.5)
    - Unity Convention, 1956 June 8-10 and 1957, 9 black-and-white photographs (Box 12, Folder M351.6)
    - Unity Convention, 1957 Jan.-Feb. 21, 6 black-and-white photographs (Box 12, Folder M351.7)
    - Unity Convention, 1957, 6 black-and-white photographs and 1 duotone plate (Box 12, Folder M351.8)
      Duotone plate is a small photographic portrait of Agnes McPhail.
    - Unity Convention, 1957, 3 black-and-white photographs (Box 12, Folder M351.9)
    - Vienna, Austria, circa 1930s, 4 black-and-white photographs (Box 12, Folder M352)
    - Viet Nam Protests, 1965, Berkeley, Cal., 1965 Mar. 22-23 and 1965, 12 black-and-white photographs (Box 12, Folder M353.1)
    - Viet Nam Protests, 1965, Berkeley, Cal., 1965 Mar. 22-23 and Aug. 1965, 8 black-and-white photographs (Box 12, Folder M353.2)
    - Workers Defense League - 1940, 1940, 5 black-and-white photographs (Box 12, Folder M354)
    - A Yearbook -- U.S.A. Manual of Peace, 1949 June 20, black-and-white photograph (Box 12, Folder M355)
    - Youth and Y.P.S.L, 1935 Apr. 13, 1960 May 20, and undated, 6 black-and-white photographs (Box 12, Folder M356)
    - Y.P.S.L. Group, 1935, black-and-white photograph (Box 12, Folder M357)
    - Wilhelm-Leuschner -- Haus, [Berlin - Dahlem] 1900s, black-and-white photograph (Box 12, Folder M358)
    - National Headquarters of Socialist Party, Chicago, March 1919 -- Oct., 1920, Mar. 1919 -- Oct. 1920, black-and-white photograph (Box 12, Folder M359)
    - Green Corn Rebellion, Oklahoma, 1917, 1917, 4 black-and-white photographs (Box 12, Folder M360)
    - Home of Eugene V. Debs, 1983 Dec., color photograph (Box 12, Folder M361)
    - National Farm Labor Union, 1948, 1949, and 1954 Aug., 2 black-and-white photographs (Box 12, Folder M362)
    - National Farm Labor Union - Di Giorgio Strike, California, 1947-1948, 1948 June 4 and 1948, 3 black-and-white photographs (Box 12, Folder M363)
      The last photograph depicts James Price after he was shot -- graphic content.
    - Southern Tenant Farmers Union, 1945 and 1900s, 5 black-and-white photographs (Box 12, Folder M364)
    - 1st Unity Convention, Indianapolis 1901, 1901 (Box 39)
      card photograph
    - National Headquarters of Socialist Party, Chicago, March 1919-October 1920, 1919 Mar.-1920 Oct., card photograph (Box 50)
    - Unity Convention, 1957, 1 black-and-white poster (Box 50)
      Small poster with portraits of many notable Socialist speakers and leaders. Removed from M351.1-9 to the Oversize Series.
  - People, 2
    - Antonini, Luigi, 1957 and 1900s, 4 black-and-white photographs (Box 12, Folder M365)
    - Bebel, August, undated, postcard (Box 12, Folder M366)
    - Bernstein, Julius and Arthur, 1956 June 8-10, black-and-white photograph (Box 12, Folder M367)
    - Bloom, Bob, 1956 June 8-10, 2 black-and-white photographs (Box 12, Folder M368)
    - Boston Anti-War Strikes, 1935 Apr. 12 and 1938, 3 black-and-white photographs (Box 12, Folder M369)
    - Branstetter, Otto, and National Executive Committee (?), 1900s, black-and-white photograph (Box 12, Folder M370)
    - Buck, Pearl (Sydenstricker), 1943 Sept. 8, black-and-white photograph (Box 12, Folder M371)